Guide to the Frederick R. Koch Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Name List
  - Wagner, Richard
    - MUSIC
      - Attente (song)
        - Printed score (clipping from Europa ), 1842
          FRKF 1045c
      - Les deux grenadiers (song)
        See: Attente (song), box 336, folder 1942
      - Extase (song)
        See: Attente (songs), box 336, folder 1941
      - Lohengrin (opera)
        - Libretto, 1845 Nov 27
          FRKF 1035
      - Die Meistersinger von Nürnberg (opera)
        - Morgenlich leuchtend im rosigen Schein: vocal line, 1866 Dec 24
          Accompanied by presentation inscription from Eva Chamberlain- Wagner to Arturo Toscanini
          FRKF 233
      - Mignonne (song)
      - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung (opera)
        - Early version titled "Siegfrieds Tod": libretto, with music quotation, 1848 Nov 12-28 (Box 59, Folder 1355)
          FRKF 334
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Marriage announcement, 1870 Aug 25 (Box 59, Folder 1356)
        FRKF 786
  - Walpole, Hugh, Sir
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Dunkels, M., [1917 Oct 1] (Box 59, Folder 1357)
  - Walton, William
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Evans, Edwin, [1942 May 13] (Box 59, Folder 1358)
        FRKF 1069
      - Kochno, Boris, 1949-50 (Box 59, Folder 1359)
        FRKF 1391a
      - Lutyens, Elisabeth, 1945-76 (Box 59, Folder 1360)
        FRKF 1051
    - MUSIC
      - Anniversary Fanfare (brass and percussion)
        - Score, [1973]
          FRKF 615
      - Anon in Love (songs for voice and guitar)
        - Version for voice and orchestra: score, [1971]
          FRKF 633
      - Antiphon (chorus and organ)
        - Score, 1977
          FRKF 618
      - As You Like It (film music)
        - Score and drafts, [1936]
          FRKF 608
        - Excerpt titled "Under the Greenwood Tree": short score, [1936]
          FRKF 636
      - The Battle of Britain (film music)
        - Excerpts titled "14.M.3" and "Introduction to March for Record": scores, mostly in holograph, [1969]
          FRKF 585
        - Other sections: scores in holograph, including photocopies, [1969]
      - The Bear (opera)
        - Incomplete vocal score, [1965-67]
          FRKF 604
      - Cantico del sole (chorus)
        - Score, [1973-74]
          FRKF 616
      - Capriccio burlesco (orchestra)
        - Score and drafts, 1968 Sep 5
          FRKF 598
      - Child's Song
        - Score, 1918 Jul
          FRKF 1334
      - Christopher Columbus (incidental music)
        - Score, [1942]
          FRKF 623
      - Concerto, viola, orchestra
        - Original version: score, [1929]
          FRKF 586a
        - Revised version: score, [1961]
          FRKF 586b
      - Concerto, violin, orchestra
        - Revised version: score and analysis, 1943
          FRKF 597
      - Concerto, violoncello, orchestra
        - Sketches in short and full score, [1955-56]
          FRKF 627
      - Coronation Te Deum
        - Short score, [1953]
          FRKF 629
      - Crown Imperial (orchestra)
        - Short score, n.d.
          FRKF 595a
        - Score in holograph, including facsimiles, [1937]
          FRKF 595b
      - Devoirs de vacances (ballet)
        Finale for a ballet on Music for Children
        - Excerpt titled "Galop final": short score, [1949] (Box 59, Folder 1361)
          FRKF 624d
      - Duets for Children (piano)
        - Music for piano, [1940]
          FRKF 624a
        - Version for piano, 4 hands: score, 1940
          FRKF 624b
      - Escape Me Never (film music)
        - Score, [1934]
          FRKF 609
      - Façade (Entertainment) (reciter and instrumental ensemble)
        - Various movements: scores, mostly in holograph or in the hand of Constant Lambert, [ca. 1922-79]
          Includes proofs and sketches
          FRKF 638a
      - Façade (Suite no. 2) (orchestra)
        - Score, partly in holograph, n.d.
          Annotations by Constant Lambert
          FRKF 638b
      - Fanfare for the National (brass and percussion)
        - Score, [1974?]
          FRKF 617
      - The First Shoot (ballet)
        See also: Medley for Brass Band, box 295, folder 1637
        - Arrangement for brass band: score, [1981]
          FRKF 594
      - The Forsaken Merman (cantata)
        - Short score, 1916
          FRKF 1429
      - Gloria (solo voices, chorus, and orchestra)
        - Short score and drafts, [1961]
          FRKF 603b
        - Full score, [1961]
          FRKF 603a
      - Granada Preludes, Call Signs and End Music (incidential music)
        - Score, [1962]
          FRKF 601
      - Hamlet (film music)
        - Score, [1947]
          Draft score fragment from Troilus and Cressida, formerly misidentified as "Original / Ham / I.M.I," pages [8-10], moved to Troilus and Cressida (opera)/Draft fragment and revisions in full and short score, box 306, folder 1648
          FRKF 583
      - Henry V (film music)
        - Score, partly in holograph, [ca. 1943-44]
          FRKF 582
      - Improvisations on an Impromptu of Benjamin Britten (orchestra)
        - Score, [1970]
          FRKF 622
      - In Honour of the City of London (cantata)
        - Incomplete short score, [1937]
          FRKF 596
      - Johannesburg Festival Overture
        - Score and photocopied excerpts, 1956 May 31
          FRKF 627a
          FRKF 630
      - Jubilate Deo (anthem)
        - Score, [1972]
          FRKF 614
      - King Herod and the Cock (chorus)
        - Score, [1977]
          FRKF 621
      - A Litany (chorus)
        - Early version: parts for trebles 1-4, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1362)
          FRKF 591b
        - Score, 1916
          FRKF 591a
      - Love Laid His Sleepless Head (song)
        - Score, 1918 Jul
          FRKF 1333
      - A Lyke-Wake Song
        - Score, 1918 Jul
          FRKF 1351
      - Macbeth (incidental music)
        - Score, [1941-42]
          FRKF 581
      - March for A History of the English Speaking Peoples (incidental music)
        - Score, [1959]
          FRKF 632
      - Medley for Brass Band
        Includes an arrangement from The First Shoot (ballet)
        - Incomplete score, [1981]
          FRKF 612
      - Missa brevis
        - Score, 1966
          FRKF 635
      - Music for Children (orchestra)
        - Score, [1940-41]
          FRKF 624c
      - The National Anthem (orchestra)
        Arrangement of "God Save the Queen"
        - Score, [1953]
          FRKF 626
      - Orb and Sceptre (orchestra)
        - Score, 1953
          FRKF 628
      - Partita, orchestra
        - Score, [1957]
          FRKF 631
      - Passacaglia, violoncello
        - Music for violoncello, [1979-80?]
          FRKF 611
      - Portsmouth Point (orchestra)
        - Score, [1924-25]
          FRKF 588a
        - Score in the hand of Constant Lambert, [1926?]
          FRKF 588b
      - Prologo e fantasia (orchestra)
        - Score, partly in holograph, [1981-82]
          FRKF 610
      - Quartet, strings, no. 1
        - Incomplete score, 1920-22
          FRKF 590
        - Original folders, n.d.
      - Quartet, strings, no. 2, A minor
        - Score, [1947]
          FRKF 606a
      - The Quest (ballet)
        - Score, partly in holograph, [1943]
          FRKF 605b
        - Score in copyist's manuscript, with fragment in the hand of Vilem Tausky, [1943]
          FRKF 605a
      - Richard III (film music)
        - Score, with portions in short score, 1955
          FRKF 584
      - Salute to Sir Robert Mayer on His 100th Birthday (trumpets and trombones)
        Introduction to "God Save the Queen"
        - Score, [1979]
          FRKF 620
      - Scapino (orchestra)
        - Incomplete score, [1940]
          FRKF 625
      - Siesta (orchestra)
        - Revised edition: first and second proofs for set of parts, [1962]
          Accompanied by a proof for the table of contents from Five poems by Edith Sitwell (London: Duckworth, 1928)
          FRKF 1428
      - Sinfonia concertante, piano, orchestra
        - Original version: score, [1927]
          FRKF 587a
        - Revised version: score, [1943]
          FRKF 587c
        - Part for piano, mostly in copyist's manuscript, [ca. 1943]
          FRKF 587b
      - Sonata, string orchestra, A minor
        Transcription of Quartet, strings, no. 2, A minor, for string orchestra
        - Score, partly in the hand of Malcolm Arnold
          FRKF 606b
      - A Song for the Lord Mayor's Table (song cycle)
        - Short score, [1962]
          FRKF 602b
        - Arrangement for voice and orchestra: score, [1970]
          FRKF 602a
      - The Spitfire Prelude and Fugue (orchestra)
        - Score, [1942-43]
          FRKF 607
        - Original binder
      - Symphony, no. 1
        - Score, [1932-35]
          FRKF 593
      - Symphony, no. 2
        - First movement, original version: score, n.d.
          FRKF 634a
        - Score, 1959-60
          FRKF 634
      - Title Music for BBC Shakespeare Series (orchestra)
        - Opening fanfare: score, [1977]
          FRKF 619
      - Toccata, violin, piano
        - Score, [1922-23]
          FRKF 592
      - Tritons (song)
        - Score, 1920
          FRKF 589
      - Troilus and Cressida (opera)
        - Score, [1947]-54
          FRKF 580
        - Draft fragment and revisions in full and short score, 1976, n.d.
          Includes draft score fragment from end of Act III, [3] p., formerly misidentified as Hamlet, "Original / Ham / I.M.I," pages [8-10]
      - The Twelve (anthem)
        - Score, 1965
          FRKF 599
      - Variations on a Theme by Hindemith (orchestra)
        - Drafts, n.d.
          FRKF 600
        - Score, 1963 Feb 6
      - Varii capricii (orchestra)
        - Score, [1975-76]
          FRKF 613a
        - No. 5, alternative version: score, n.d.
          FRKF 613b
        - Coda for ballet version: short score, [1983 Mar] (Box 59, Folder 1363)
          FRKF 613c
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Music portfolios, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1364)
        Formerly contained some of the music listed above
  - Waugh, Evelyn
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Brewer, Joseph, [ca. 1925 May] (Box 59, Folder 1365)
        Autograph letter, signed "Evelyn," to Brewer from an unidentified correspondent. Correspondent was formerly identified as Evelyn Waugh (Sotheby's sale, 1999 December 7, lot 296)
        FRKF 1433
  - Weber, Carl Maria von
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Weber, Gottfried, 1810-26 (Box 59, Folder 1366-1369)
        Includes letters with music quotations Includes clippings from Briefe von C. M. Weber and the Münchener politische Zeitung Includes circular letter signed by Weber and: Dusch, Alexander von Gänsbacher, Johann Baptist Meyerbeer, Giacomo Weber, Gottfried
        FRKF 151
  - Whistler, James McNeill
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Rossetti, William Michael, [1867-81] (Box 59, Folder 1370)
        FRKF 637
  - Whistler, Rex
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Tennant, Stephen, 1924-37 (Box 59, Folder 1371-1373)
        Most letters include drawings
        FRKF 1310
    - DRAWINGS
      - Illustrations for Jonathan Swift, Gulliver's Travels (London: Cresset Press, 1930), 1929-1930
        Drafts in pen-and-ink and pencil; and proofs on paper and vellum, some hand-colored, with some text excerpts, for copy number I of ten copies on roman vellum, numbered I-X
  - Widor, Charles Marie
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1374)
        FRKF 662c
  - Wilde, Oscar
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Blacker, Carlos, 1897 Jul-[Aug] (Box 59, Folder 1375)
        FRKF 1205
        FRKF 1207
      - Coghlan, Rose, [1893 fall] (Box 59, Folder 1376)
        Drafts of telegrams to Coghlan and Elisabeth Marbury
        FRKF 277
      - Marbury, Elisabeth
        See: Coghlan, Rose, box 59, folder 1376
      - Ross, Robert Baldwin (to Blacker, Carlos)
        See: Writings/ De profundis, box 60, folders 1378-1380
      - Smithers, Leonard C. (Leonard Charles) (forgery), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1377)
        FRKF 1203
    - WRITINGS
      - De profundis
        - Typescript, corrected in an unidentified hand (Box 60, Folder 1378-1380)
          With slipcase, inscribed by Robert Baldwin Ross and Charles Blacker, 1934 Accompanied by letter from Ross to Blacker, 1913 May 14, and a clipping
          FRKF 1403a-b
        - Typescript, inscribed by Carlos Blacker, 1913 (Box 60, Folder 1381)
          FRKF 1403a
        - Typescript, inscribed by Carlos Blacker, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1382)
      - Other writings
        - "To L. L." (poem), [ca. 1885]
          FRKF 1008
  - Wilhelm I, German Emperor
    See: William I, German Emperor, box 60, folder 1383
  - Wilhelm II, German Emperor
    See: William II, German Emperor, box 60, folders 1384-1389
  - William I, German Emperor
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Unidentified document, 1863 Mar 17 (Box 60, Folder 1383)
  - William II, German Emperor
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      All materials: FRKF 1290
      - Montagu, Mary, 1905-14, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1384-1388)
        Includes pictorial postcards, some with photographs of William II and others
      - Montagu-Douglas-Scott, Charles Thomas, 1905 Oct 7 (Box 60, Folder 1389)
  - Wolf, Hugo
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Grohe, Oskar, 1895 Jun 24 (Box 61, Folder 1390)
        FRKF 1137
      - Potpeschnigg, Heinrich, 1897 May 17 (Box 61, Folder 1391)
        FRKF 23
    - MUSIC
      - Goethe-Lieder
        - Beherzigung: score, [1887]
          FRKF 1038
      - Ich stand in dunkeln Träumen (song)
        - Score, 1878 May 26-29
          FRKF 1140
      - Mir träumte von einem Königskind (song)
        - Score, 1878 Jun 16
          FRKF 1159
      - Wie des Mondes Abbild zittert (song)
        - Score, 1880 Feb 13
          FRKF 550
  - Wolf-Ferrari, Ermanno
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Backmeister, Walter, [1895]-1946 (Box 61, Folder 1392-1393)
        Includes postcard photograph of scene from Il campiello
        FRKF 829a
      - Backmeister, Walter, from Wolf-Ferrari, Wilhelmine, 1948-64, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1394)
        Includes photographs of Wolf-Ferrari and of his tomb
        FRKF 829b
    - MUSIC
      - Gli amanti sposi (opera)
        - Draft in short score, and sketches, 1921, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.01
      - L'amore medico (opera)
        - Draft in short score, fragment of overture in full score, and drafts, 1910-12, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.02
      - An Emma (song)
        See: Songs (1892), box 344, folder 2037
      - Aria, violin, piano
        - Incomplete score and drafts, 1900 Jul
          FRKF 1200.04
      - Le baruffe chiozzotte (orchestra)
        - Score, 1895 Mar 7
          FRKF 1200.07
      - La bona mare (opera)
        - Sketches in short score, 1940 Aug 30
          FRKF 1200.09
      - Canto notturno
        See: Songs (1896), box 344, folder 2038
      - Canzone di Dante
        - Incomplete score and drafts, 1897 Jun 4, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.11
      - Capriccio, piano
        - Music for piano, 1895 Nov
          Includes unidentified draft
          FRKF 1200.12
      - Cenerentola (opera)
        - Drafts in short and full score, mostly in holograph, 1898, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.14
      - Charfreitag (string quartet)
        - Score, titled "Charfreitag v. Wagner, Parsifal", n.d.
          FRKF 1200.73
      - Choral songs
        See: Quartina; Stornello, box 343, folder 2024
      - Concertino (English horn, strings, and two horns)
        - Full score, short score, and draft, each titled "Sonata-concertino", 1947, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.83
      - Concerto, violoncello, orchestra
        - First movement: draft in short score, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.15
      - Concerto, violoncello, orchestra, op. 31, C major
        - Score, titled "Invocation", n.d.
          FRKF 1200.29
      - La dama boba (opera)
        - Drafts in full and short score, and with additional draft material, 1937, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.17
      - Le donne curiose (opera)
        - Draft in short score, and sketches
          FRKF 1200.18
      - Die drei Röselein (song)
        - Score, [early 1900s?]
          FRKF 1200.19
      - Fantasia, orchestra
        - Score, 1895 May
          FRKF 1200.20
      - Frottola (chorus)
        - Score, [mid 1890s]
          FRKF 1200.21
      - Fugue, organ
        - Sketches of organ music, 1904 Jul 14
          FRKF 1200.24
      - Fugue, string quartet
        - Score, [mid 1890s]
          FRKF 1200.22
      - Ghiribizzi quasi Ländler (piano)
        - Music for piano, 1895 Jun
          FRKF 1200.25
      - I gioielli della Madonna (opera)
        - Drafts and sketches in short score, 1908, n.d.
          Laid in: fragment of Hauff, Wilhelm, Märchen-Almanach auf das Jahr 1826
          FRKF 1200.26
      - Das Himmelskleid (opera)
        - Drafts and sketches, 1922, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.28
      - Idillio-concertino (oboe and strings)
        - Draft, [early 1930s]
          FRKF 1200.82
      - Invocazione (violoncello and orchestra)
        See: Concerto, violoncello, orchestra, op. 31, C major, box 229, folder 1571
      - Irene (opera)
        - Drafts and sketches in short and full score, mostly in holograph, 1895, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1395)
          FRKF 1200.30
      - Larghetto, piano trio
        - Score, [after 1900?]
          FRKF 1200.31
      - Mailied (song for voice, violin, violoncello, and piano)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.33
      - Neig schöne Knospe (song)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.34
      - Ogni pena più spettata (song)
        - Vocal line, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1396)
          Possibly related to Canto notturno in Songs (1896)
      - Oh! Menschenherz, was ist dein Glück? (song)
      - Passacaglia, organ
        See also: Symphony, C major, box 345, folder 2042
        - Incomplete music for organ, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.35
      - La passione (chorus)
        - Score, 1906
          FRKF 1200.36
      - Pezzi, orchestra
        - Drafts and sketches in short score
          FRKF 1200.38
      - Pezzi, organ
        - Music for organ, two copies, 1895 Dec 14
          FRKF 1200.39
      - Phantasietanz (piano)
        - Music for piano, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.37
      - Prelude, piano
        - Music for piano, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.41
      - Prelude and fugue, organ
        - Organ music, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.42
      - Quartet, strings
        - Drafts and sketches
          FRKF 1200.62
      - Quartet, strings, op. 23, E minor
        - Draft and parts for violins I and II, 1940 Feb-May
          FRKF 1200.43
      - Quartina; Stornello (chorus)
        - Scores, [1890s?]
          FRKF 1200.61a-b
      - I quattro rusteghi (opera)
        - Drafts and sketches in short score
          FRKF 1200.45
      - Quintet, violins, violas, violoncello
        - Draft, [early 1930s?]
          FRKF 1200.75
      - Il riso (chorus and piano)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.46
      - Rispetti, op. 11 (songs)
        - Sketches and score
          FRKF 1200.47
      - Rispetti, op. 12 (songs)
        - Draft, 1902 Oct 24
          FRKF 1200.48
      - Salmo 100 (song)
      - Scena di Orfeo (tenor, chorus, and piano)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.50
      - Il segreto di Susanna (opera)
        - Fragment and drafts in short score
          FRKF 1200.51
      - Septet, piano, winds, strings
        - Drafts, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.52
      - Serenata (song)
      - Sextet, violins, violas, violoncellos
        - Score, 1895 Mar
          FRKF 1200.53
        - Fourth movement: draft, 1894 Oct
      - Sextet, woodwinds, horn
        - Fragment in short score, 1900 Oct 29
          FRKF 1200.54
      - Sly (opera)
        - Drafts and sketches in short score, 1926, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.55
      - Sonata-concertino (English horn, strings, and two horns)
        See: Concertino (English horn, strings, and two horns), box 228, folder 1570
      - Sonata, organ
        Drafts
        FRKF 1200.56
      - Sonatas, piano
        - Music for piano, n.d.
          Sonatina, piano
          Sonata, piano, C major
          Sonata, piano, C minor
          FRKF 1200.59
      - Sonata, piano, C major
        See: Sonatas, piano, box 344, folder 2034
      - Sonata, piano, C minor
      - Sonata, violin, piano, A minor
        - Drafts, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.57
      - Sonata, violin, piano, G minor
        - Draft, 1895 Jun
          FRKF 1200.58
      - Sonatina, piano
        See: Sonata, piano, box 344, folder 2034
      - Sonetto
      - Songs (1892)
        - Score, 1892 Dec 16
          An Emma
          Oh! Menschenherz, was ist dein Glück?
          Salmo 100
          Serenata
          Stornello
          Strimpellata
          FRKF 1200.03a-f
      - Songs (1896)
        See also: Ogni pena più spettata, box 61, folder 1396
        - Scores and fragment, 1896 Sep-Dec
          Canto notturno
          Sonetto
          Zingarella
          FRKF 1200.60a-c
      - Songs (chorus)
        See also: Quartina, Stornello, box 343, folder 2024
        - Scores, titled "Due canti", n.d.
          FRKF 1200.10
      - Stornello (song)
      - Strimpellata (song)
      - Suite-concertino, bassoon, string orchestra
        - Drafts in full and short score
          FRKF 1200.63
        - Arrangement for violin and string orchestra: part for violin, [ca. 1933]
          FRKF 1200.63a
      - La Sulamite (solo voices, chorus, and orchestra)
        - Draft in short score, 1898 Aug 18-27
          FRKF 1200.64
      - Symphony, C major
        - Final movement: drafts, n.d.
          Includes unidentified sketches, possibly relating to Passacaglia, organ
          FRKF 1200.65
      - Symphony, E minor
        - Drafts and sketches in full and short score, 1894, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.66
      - Symphony, F minor
        - Drafts in short score, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.67
      - Symphony, F-sharp minor
        - Draft, n.d.
          Includes possibly unrelated drafts
          FRKF 1200.68
      - Talitha Kumi (solo voices, chorus, and orchestra)
        - Drafts in full and short score, 1898 Oct 9-26
          FRKF 1200.69
      - Totentanz (chorus and orchestra)
        - Incomplete short score, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.72
      - La vedova scaltra (opera)
        - Draft and sketches in short score, 1929 Apr-Oct
          FRKF 1200.77
      - La vita nuova (cantata)
        - Draft in short score, 1901 Apr 24
          FRKF 1200.78
      - Vom Berge (song)
        - Incomplete draft, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.79
      - Zingarella (song)
      - Unidentified
        See also: Capriccio, piano, box 342, folder 2005
        See also; Songs (1892), box 344, folder 2037
        See also: Symphony, F-sharp minor, box 345, folder 2045
        See also: La vita nuova (cantata), box 242, folder 1584
        See also: Vom Berge (song), box 345, folder 2047
        See also: Unidentified/Piano music, waltzes, box 346, folder 2057
        See also: Exercises/Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, Paride ed Elena, box 346, folder 2061
        - Fugue in E minor: draft, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.23
        - Instrumental and vocal music: notes, sketches, and drafts, 1945, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1397)
        - Opera: draft in short score, 1932 Jul
          FRKF 1200.74
        - Orchestra music, scherzo: draft in short score, n.d.
        - Orchestra music, theme and variations: draft in short score
          FRKF 1200.71
        - Organ music, titled "Cantata 104, Bach", n.d.
          FRKF 1200.06
        - Organ music: sketches, 1918, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.76
        - Piano music in E minor: drafts, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.40
        - Piano music in five movements, [early 20th c?]
          FRKF 1200.13
        - Piano music, theme and variations
          FRKF 1200.70
        - Piano music in two movements, with sketches, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.32